

Salesforce Administrator – UX / UI Designer

Details (419) 309-1531

AlexisNFrisch@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/alexis-frisch

Skills

Salesforce Development (SLDS)

UX and UI Design

Full Adobe Creative Suite – InDesign, Photoshop, XD, After Effects

HTML 5 / CSS / JS

Microsoft Office Suite – Excel, Word

Fearless in the Face of Challenges

Insatiably Curious

Decent Piano Player

Profile

Passionate UX Designer with experience in the Adobe Creative Suite for mock-ups/wire framing and Salesforce Administrator with experience in CRM management and training within the Lightning platform. Recreationally passionate about special effects makeup and animatronic creatures, spending time with family, and all things Halloween.

Employment History

Product Design Specialist SimplyHome - Remote

March 2020 - Present

CRM Development, Programming, and Enhancement - Salesforce Lightning Developer (including light Apex) - Salesforce User Management, Report and Dashboard Building, Workflow Creation and Process Optimization - UI/UX Design - Quality Assurance Specialist - Beta Test Coordinator - Data Visualization Specialist

Operations Coordinator SimplyHome - Arden, NC

July 2018 - March 2020

Administrative Assistant Supervisor - Development and Management of Representative Onboarding, Including Planning and Hosting Monthly Roundtables and Implementation of a Dedicated Web Community - Report Monthly on Business Development KPIs - Business Flow Management - Initial Contact for all New Providers, Partners, and Consumers - Marketing and Design of Consumer-Facing and Internal Content

Operations Coordinator ResortQuest by Wyndham- Miramar Beach, FL

March 2015 - July 2018

Homeowner Liaison Duties - Monthly Forecasting/Preliminary Budgeting - Vendor Invoice and Purchasing Card Coding and Processing - SOX Compliance - Operational Support - Office Supply Management - Housekeeping and Maintenance Support

Education

Tech Talent South - Arden, NC

April 2019

Code Immersion – HTML, CSS, IS, Ruby, Rails, GitHub

Bowling Green State University - OH

2011-2015

Bachelor's Degree - Tourism, Leisure, and Event Planning